(Raj:)Go out with me on one date
and I promise you you'll see.
(Leonard:)Okay.
(Girl:)Text me.
Bye.
(Raj:)You won't regret it.
I'm the most pathetic guy you've ever met.
(Raj:)And that, boys and girls, is how it's done.
(Penny(as Blanche DuBois):)You love her very much, don't you?
(Raj:)Yes.
I think you have great capacity for devotion.
You will be Ionely
when she passes on, won't you?
(Penny:)I understand what that is.
- To be Ionely?
- She's pretty good, huh?
(Sheldon:)She is.
(Sheldon:)But when do they get to the part
about streetcars?
(Penny(as Blanche):)When I was a very young girl.
(Penny(as Blanche):)When I was 16 years old,
I made the discovery:
(Raj:)Love.
(Penny(as Blanche):)All at once and much, much too completely.
It was like you turned
a blinding light on something...
(Penny(as Blanche):)...that had always been half a shadow.
(Penny(as Blanche):)That's how it struck the world for me.
(Penny(as Blanche):)But I was unlucky.
(Penny(as Blanche):)Deluded.
- She's remarkable.
- She really is.
(Amy:)Our Penny's a star.
(Sheldon:)How can she remember all those lines...
(Sheldon:)...but as a waitress, she can't remember
no tomato on my hamburger?